Lowell Folklife Project collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series I: Manuscripts
  - Subseries XI: Publications and Ephemera
    - Programs (Box-folder 9/153)
      Program and flyer about National Museum of American History's conference on American labor history; program about National Museum of American History's exhibit, lecture, and tour of Daughters-of-Freemen 19th Century Mill Girls.
    - Samuel P. Howes, Portrait Painter Exhibition Catalog at the Whistler House Museum, Lowell, 1986 (Box-folder 9/154)
    - Schell, Marina Sampas, Compiler. That Was the Way It Was - A Selection of Charles G. Sampas' "Sampascoopies Lowell History Columns" (Lowell: Marina Sampas Schell, 1986) (Box-folder 9/155)
    - Talbert Manuscript Song Collection - Reference Copy (Box-folder 9/156)
      Handwritten songbook by Matilda Lemire Talbert.
    - Talbert Manuscript Song Collection - Original, circa 1976 (Box-folder 9/157)
      Handwritten songbook by Matilda Lemire Talbert
    - U.S. Department of the Interior Geological Survey. Index to Topographical Maps of Massachusetts, Rhode Island, and Connecticut. Date: May 1980 (Box-folder 9/158)
- Series II: Computer Disks, Fourteen floppy disks (in XYWrite) and one 3-1/2-inch disk (Box 9)
  Labeled LFP-1 through LFP-14 with (1) collection inventory (LFPinven.doc) and (2) index to sound recordings (LFPindex.tbl), in WordPerfect 5.1, printout in folder 65.
- Series III: Sound Recordings
  - Audiocassettes, 95 sound cassettes
    - Massey, John, 1987-12-01, LFP-MB-A001
    - Massey, John, 1987-12-01, LFP-MB-A002
    - Southeast Asian restaurant and store, 1987-12-02, LFP-MB-A003
    - Maha Visantara Jataka Desana, 1987-12-12, LFP-MB-A004
    - Maha Visantara Jataka Desana, 1987-12-12, LFP-MB-A005
    - Franco-American Male Chorus, 1987-09-08, LFP-CC-A001
    - Mello, Deolinda, 1976-03-25, LFP-CC-A002
    - Lagasse, Yvonne, 1987-08-11, LFP-CC-A003
    - Lagasse, Yvonne, 1987-08-11, LFP-CC-A004
    - Lagasse, Yvonne, 1987-08-11, LFP-CC-A005
    - Lagasse, Yvonne, 1987-08-11, LFP-CC-A006
    - Lagasse, Yvonne, 1987-08-11, LFP-CC-A007
    - Lagasse, Yvonne, 1987-08-11, LFP-CC-A008
    - Lagasse, Yvonne, 1987-08-11, LFP-CC-A009
    - Lagasse, Yvonne, 1987-08-11, LFP-CC-A010
    - Lagasse, Yvonne, 1987-08-11, LFP-CC-A011
    - Lagasse, Yvonne, 1987-08-11, LFP-CC-A012
    - Lagasse, Yvonne, 1987-08-11, LFP-CC-A013
    - Lagasse, Yvonne, 1987-08-11, LFP-CC-A014
    - Lagasse, Yvonne, 1987-08-11, LFP-CC-A015
    - Lagasse, Yvonne, 1987-08-11, LFP-CC-A016
    - Lagasse, Yvonne, 1987-08-11, LFP-CC-A017
    - Lagasse, Yvonne, 1987-08-11, LFP-CC-A018
    - Lagasse, Yvonne, 1987-08-11, LFP-CC-A019
    - Lagasse, Yvonne, 1987-08-11, LFP-CC-A020
    - Lagasse, Yvonne, 1987-08-11, LFP-CC-A021
    - Lagasse, Yvonne, 1987-08-11, LFP-CC-A022
    - Dooley, Greg, 1987-11-17, LFP-CC-A023
    - Didomenico, John, 1987-07-14, LFP-DD-A001
    - Didomenico, John, 1987-07-14, LFP-DD-A002
    - St. Peter's church meeting, 1988-01-29, LFP-DD-A003
    - Brunelle, Roger, 1988-02-15, LFP-DD-A004
    - Brunelle, Roger, 1988-02-15, LFP-DD-A005
    - Barros, Manuel Jr., 1987-11-15, LFP-BF-A001
    - Barros, Manual Sr., 1987-11-16, LFP-BF-A002
    - Barros, Manual Sr., 1987-11-16, LFP-BF-A003
    - Oliveira, Gabriela, 1987-11-17, LFP-BF-A004
    - Silva, Maria, 1987-11-17, LFP-BF-A005
    - Simao, Jose, 1987-11-17, LFP-BF-A006
    - Corvalno, Francisco (Frank), 1987-11-18, LFP-BF-A007
    - Figueira, Manuel and Umbelina, 1987-11-19, LFP-BF-A008
    - Loreto Feast Committee, 1987-11-20, LFP-BF-A009
    - De Sousa, Henry, 1987-12-03, LFP-BF-A010
    - Garcia, Anthony, 1987-12-04, LFP-BF-A011
    - Estacio, Bob, 1987-12-04, LFP-BF-A012
    - Cunha, Maria, 1987-12-04, LFP-BF-A013
    - Nieves, Jose and Ramon, 1987-08-20, LFP-MM-A001
    - Rosas, Tomas, 1987-10-19, LFP-MM-A002
    - Rosas, Tomas, 1987-10-19, LFP-MM-A003
    - Fee, Father Jaime, 1987-10-21, LFP-MM-A004
    - Fee, Father Jaime, 1987-10-21, LFP-MM-A005
    - Luna, Felix, 1987-10-21, LFP-MM-A006
    - Figaroa, Bienvenida, 1987-10-23, LFP-MM-A007
    - Colon, Severa, 1987-10-23, LFP-MM-A008
    - Rivera, Hipolito, 1987-10-26, LFP-MM-A009
    - Zapata, Sister Angela Maria, 1987-10-26, LFP-MM-A010
    - Finn, Fr. Seamus, 1987-10-27, LFP-MM-A011
    - Luna, Felix and Jose, 1987-12-12, LFP-MM-A012
    - Cartagena, Carmen, 1987-12-12, LFP-MM-A013
    - Fee, Father Jaime, 1988-02-22, LFP-MM-A014
    - Martinez, Gladys, 1988-02-22, LFP-MM-A015
    - Evangelical Reach, 1988-02-22, LFP-MM-A016
    - Fee, Father Jaime, 1988-02-23, LFP-MM-A017
    - Masso, Alba, 1988-02-23, LFP-MM-A018
    - Silva, Ramon, 1988-02-23, LFP-MM-A019
    - Silva, Ramon, 1988-02-23, LFP-MM-A020
    - Hernandez, Cecilio, 1988-02-24, LFP-MM-A021
    - Bermudez, Angel, 1987-02-24, LFP-MM-A022
    - Fernandez, Rademas, 1988-02-29, LFP-MM-A023
    - Hernandez, Cecilio, 1988-02-29, LFP-MM-A024
    - Paquette, Adrien, 1987-08-19, LFP-TR-A001
    - Vasquez, Leo, 1987-08-20, LFP-TR-A002
    - Dracut softball league playoffs, 1987-08-25, LFP-TR-A003
    - English as a second language class, 1987-09-10, LFP-TR-A004
    - Poolsin Pat, 1987-05-03, LFP-RA-A001
    - Sameth Chea, 1987-06-15, LFP-RA-A002
    - Nhak Chann, 1987-06-05, LFP-RA-A003
    - Sao Khon (Venerable), 1987-06-19, LFP-RA-A004
    - Douangmany Malavong, 1987-05-10, LFP-RA-A005
    - Khoxayo wedding guests, 1987-06-13, LFP-RA-A006
    - Phosy Sengsiri, 1987-07-07, LFP-RA-A007
    - Bouapha Bouala, 1987-07-15, LFP-RA-A008
    - Mary Vu, 1986-10-28, LFP-RA-A009
    - Thong Pham, 1987-04-26, LFP-RA-A010
    - Gia Pho, 1987-05-23, LFP-RA-A011
    - Xuandung Pham, 1987-05-22, LFP-RA-A012
    - Khanh Nguyen Ong, 1987-06-10, LFP-RA-A013
    - Khanh Nguyen Ong, 1987-06-10, LFP-RA-A014
    - Khamsone Silavong, 1987-07-23, LFP-RA-A015
    - O'Brien, Sherman, 1987-09-22, LFP-DT-A001
    - Gagnon, Raymond, 1987-09-24, LFP-DT-A002
    - Dristiliaris, William, 1987-10-15, LFP-EW-A001
    - Langlois, Antoine, 1987-11-11, LFP-EW-A002
    - Kazalski, Paul, 1987-11-14, LFP-EW-A003
    - Tzanetakos, Julia, 1987-12-08, LFP-EW-A004
  - Reel-to-Reel Tapes, 247 sound tape reels: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in.
    - Flynn, Larry, 1987-11-02, LFP-MB-R001
    - Flynn, Larry, 1987-11-02, LFP-MB-R002
    - Flynn, Larry, 1987-11-02, LFP-MB-R003
    - Sao, Narin, 1987-11-04, LFP-MB-R004
    - Sao, Narin, 1987-11-04, LFP-MB-R005
    - Sayasane, Phomma, 1987-11-04, LFP-MB-R006
    - Sayasane, Phomma, 1987-11-04, LFP-MB-R007
    - Hul, Narong, 1987-11-09, LFP-MB-R008
    - Hul, Narong, 1987-11-09, LFP-MB-R009
    - Antonaccio, Joseph, 1987-11-16, LFP-MB-R010
    - Antonaccio, Joseph, 1987-11-16, LFP-MB-R011
    - Theobold, Theresa, 1987-12-17, LFP-MB-R012
    - Theobold, Theresa, 1987-12-17, LFP-MB-R013
    - Theobold, Theresa, 1987-12-17, LFP-MB-R014
    - Kuch, Sergent, 1987-12-21, LFP-MB-R015
    - Massey, John, 1987-12-22, LFP-MB-R016
    - Schmidt, Steve, 1987-12-22, LFP-MB-R017
    - Schmidt, Steve, 1987-12-22, LFP-MB-R018
    - Vu, Ahn (Hoang), 1988-01-07, LFP-MB-R019
    - Vu, Ahn (Hoang), 1988-01-07, LFP-MB-R020
    - Lagasse, Yvonne, 1987-08-11, LFP-DD-R001
    - Lagasse, Yvonne, 1987-08-11, LFP-DD-R002
    - Franco-American picnic, 1987-08-22, LFP-DD-R003
    - Franco-American picnic, 1987-08-22, LFP-DD-R004
    - Franco-American picnic, 1987-08-22, LFP-DD-R005
    - Franco-American picnic, 1987-08-22, LFP-DD-R006
    - Franco-American picnic, 1987-08-22, LFP-DD-R007
    - Mogan, Patrick, 1987-08-27, LFP-DD-R008
    - Mogan, Patrick, 1987-08-27, LFP-DD-R009
    - Mogan, Patrick, 1987-08-27, LFP-DD-R010
    - Trairatanaram Temple Ceremony, 1987-08-30, LFP-DD-R011
    - Trairatanaram Temple Ceremony, 1987-08-30, LFP-DD-R012
    - Trairatanaram Temple Ceremony, 1987-08-30, LFP-DD-R013
    - Trairatanaram Temple Ceremony, 1987-08-30, LFP-DD-R014
    - Trairatanaram Temple Ceremony, 1987-08-30, LFP-DD-R015
    - Trairatanaram Temple Ceremony, 1987-08-30, LFP-DD-R016
    - Trairatanaram Temple Ceremony, 1987-08-30, LFP-DD-R017
    - The Franco-Americans, 1987-09-16, LFP-DD-R018
    - The Franco-Americans, 1987-09-16, LFP-DD-R019
    - The Franco-Americans, 1987-09-16, LFP-DD-R020
    - Cambodian musicians: Sorn Veuk Home, 1987-09-20, LFP-DD-R021
    - Cambodian musicians: Sorn Veuk Home, 1987-09-20, LFP-DD-R022
    - Cambodian musicians: Sorn Veuk Home, 1987-09-20, LFP-DD-R023
    - Cambodian musicians: Sorn Veuk Home, 1987-09-20, LFP-DD-R024
    - Cambodian wedding, 1987-09-26, LFP-DD-R025
    - Cambodian wedding, 1987-09-26, LFP-DD-R026
    - Cambodian wedding, 1987-09-26, LFP-DD-R027
    - Cambodian wedding, 1987-09-27, LFP-DD-R028
    - Cambodian wedding, 1987-09-27, LFP-DD-R029
    - Cambodian wedding, 1987-09-27, LFP-DD-R030
    - Cambodian wedding, 1987-09-27, LFP-DD-R031
    - Ethnic Covenant dinner, 1987-10-24, LFP-DD-R032
    - Ethnic Covenant dinner, 1987-10-24, LFP-DD-R033
    - Ethnic Covenant dinner, 1987-10-24, LFP-DD-R034
    - Mogan, Patrick J., 1987-11-05, LFP-DD-R035
    - Mogan, Patrick J., 1987-11-05, LFP-DD-R036
    - Mogan, Patrick J., 1987-11-05, LFP-DD-R037
    - Mogan, Patrick J., 1987-11-05, LFP-DD-R038
    - Peskin, Sarah, 1987-11-05, LFP-DD-R039
    - Peskin, Sarah, 1987-11-05, LFP-DD-R040
    - Peskin, Sarah, 1987-11-05, LFP-DD-R041
    - Peskin, Sarah, 1987-11-05, LFP-DD-R042
    - Campbell, James, 1987-12-02, LFP-DD-R043
    - Campbell, James, 1987-12-02, LFP-DD-R044
    - Silva, Fr. Eusebio, 1988-01-25, LFP-DD-R045
    - Silva, Fr. Eusebio, 1988-01-25, LFP-DD-R046
    - Silva, Fr. Eusebio, 1988-01-25, LFP-DD-R047
    - Greek Letters Day, Hellenic Center, 1988-01-31, LFP-DD-R048
    - Greek Letters Day, Hellenic Center, 1988-01-31, LFP-DD-R049
    - Greek Letters Day, Hellenic Center, 1988-01-31, LFP-DD-R050
    - Mavrick, James C. and Eugenia J., 1988-02-13, LFP-DD-R051
    - Mavrick, James C. and Eugenia J., 1988-02-13, LFP-DD-R052
    - Mavrick, James C. and Eugenia J., 1988-02-13, LFP-DD-R053
    - Mavrick, James C. and Eugenia J., 1988-02-13, LFP-DD-R054
    - Carnaval, Holy Ghost Park, 1988-02-13, LFP-DD-R055
    - Carnaval, Holy Ghost Park, 1988-02-13, LFP-DD-R056
    - Carnaval, Holy Ghost Park, 1988-02-13, LFP-DD-R057
    - Carnaval, Holy Ghost Park, 1988-02-13, LFP-DD-R058
    - Carnaval, Holy Ghost Park, 1988-02-13, LFP-DD-R059
    - Carnaval, St. Anthony's Church, 1988-02-14, LFP-DD-R060
    - Carnaval, St. Anthony's Church, 1988-02-14, LFP-DD-R061
    - Carnaval, St. Anthony's Church, 1988-02-14, LFP-DD-R062
    - Carnaval, St. Anthony's Church, 1988-02-14, LFP-DD-R063
    - Good Friday Procession and Mass, 1988-04-01, LFP-DD-R064
    - Good Friday Procession and Mass, 1988-04-01, LFP-DD-R065
    - Good Friday Procession and Mass, 1988-04-01, LFP-DD-R066
    - Good Friday Procession and Mass, 1988-04-01, LFP-DD-R067
    - Good Friday Procession and Mass, 1988-04-01, LFP-DD-R068
    - Good Friday Procession and Mass, 1988-04-01, LFP-DD-R069
    - Park Rangers, 1988-04-07, LFP-DD-R070
    - Park Rangers, 1988-04-07, LFP-DD-R071
    - Park Rangers, 1988-04-07, LFP-DD-R072
    - Park Rangers, 1988-04-07, LFP-DD-R073
    - Holy Trinity Good Friday Vigil, 1988-04-08, LFP-DD-R074
    - Holy Trinity Good Friday Vigil, 1988-04-08, LFP-DD-R075
    - Holy Trinity Easter Service, 1988-04-09, LFP-DD-R076
    - Holy Trinity Easter Service, 1988-04-09, LFP-DD-R077
    - Holy Trinity Easter Service, 1988-04-09, LFP-DD-R078
    - Holy Trinity Easter Service, 1988-04-09, LFP-DD-R079
    - Holy Trinity Easter Service, 1988-04-09, LFP-DD-R080
    - Fado music at IV Seasons, 1987-11-14, LFP-BF-R001
    - Fado music at IV Seasons, 1987-11-14, LFP-BF-R002
    - Puerto Rican Festival, 1987-08-20, LFP-MM-R001
    - Puerto Rican Festival, 1987-08-20, LFP-MM-R002
    - Puerto Rican Festival, 1987-08-20, LFP-MM-R003
    - Luna, Medina, Nieves, 1987-10-22, LFP-MM-R004
    - Luna, Medina, Nieves, 1987-10-22, LFP-MM-R005
    - Luna, Medina, Nieves, 1987-10-22, LFP-MM-R006
    - Church of the Nazarene, 1987-10-25, LFP-MM-R007
    - Church of the Nazarene, 1987-10-25, LFP-MM-R008
    - Church of the Nazarene, 1987-10-25, LFP-MM-R009
    - Luna, Medina, Rosado, 1987-10-25, LFP-MM-R010
    - Luna, Medina, Rosado, 1987-10-25, LFP-MM-R011
    - Oblate Hispanic Mission Procession, 1987-10-31, LFP-MM-R012
    - Oblate Hispanic Mission Procession, 1987-10-31, LFP-MM-R013
    - Oblate Hispanic Mission Procession, 1987-10-31, LFP-MM-R014
    - Oblate Hispanic Mission Procession, 1987-10-31, LFP-MM-R015
    - Pig Roast, 1987-12-12, LFP-MM-R016
    - Prevost, Winthrop, 1987-08-12, LFP-MN-R001
    - Prevost, Winthrop, 1987-08-12, LFP-MN-R002
    - Hogan, Mary, 1987-08-12, LFP-MN-R003
    - Hogan, Mary, 1987-08-12, LFP-MN-R004
    - Dempsey, Dorothy, 1987-08-13, LFP-MN-R005
    - Dempsey, Dorothy, 1987-08-13, LFP-MN-R006
    - Dempsey, Dorothy, 1987-08-13, LFP-MN-R007
    - Inglis, George and Rose, 1987-08-14, LFP-MN-R008
    - Inglis, George and Rose, 1987-08-14, LFP-MN-R009
    - Miskell, Millie, 1987-08-17, LFP-MN-R010
    - Miskell, Millie, 1987-08-17, LFP-MN-R011
    - Miskell, Millie, 1987-08-17, LFP-MN-R012
    - Miskell, Millie, 1987-08-17, LFP-MN-R013
    - Flanagan, William and Dorothy, 1987-08-17, LFP-MN-R014
    - Flanagan, William and Dorothy, 1987-08-17, LFP-MN-R015
    - Merritt, George, 1987-08-20, LFP-MN-R016
    - Merritt, George, 1987-08-20, LFP-MN-R017
    - Merritt, George, 1987-08-20, LFP-MN-R018
    - Cleary, Edward, 1987-08-20, LFP-MN-R019
    - Cleary, Edward, 1987-08-20, LFP-MN-R020
    - Bailey, Reverend Paul, 1987-08-24, LFP-MN-R021
    - Bailey, Reverend Paul, 1987-08-24, LFP-MN-R022
    - Blazonis, Michael, 1987-08-24, LFP-MN-R023
    - Blazonis, Michael, 1987-08-24, LFP-MN-R024
    - Blazonis, Michael, 1987-08-24, LFP-MN-R025
    - Luz, Adrien: Luz Granite Co., 1987-08-25, LFP-MN-R026
    - Luz, Adrien: Luz Granite Co., 1987-08-25, LFP-MN-R027
    - Luz, Adrien: Luz Granite Co., 1987-08-25, LFP-MN-R028
    - Dion, Ann Marie, 1987-08-26, LFP-MN-R029
    - Dion, Ann Marie, 1987-08-26, LFP-MN-R030
    - Bingo, St. Louis Church, 1987-08-26, LFP-MN-R031
    - Bingo, St. Louis Church, 1987-08-26, LFP-MN-R032
    - Bingo, St. Louis Church, 1987-08-26, LFP-MN-R033
    - Klimczak, Reverend Joseph, 1987-08-27, LFP-MN-R034
    - Klimczak, Reverend Joseph, 1987-08-27, LFP-MN-R035
    - Klimczak, Reverend Joseph, 1987-08-27, LFP-MN-R036
    - Soucy, Robert (Reverend), 1987-08-27, LFP-MN-R037
    - Soucy, Robert (Reverend), 1987-08-27, LFP-MN-R038
    - Levallee, Gerard; Burns, Thomas, 1987-09-01, LFP-MN-R039
    - Levallee, Gerard; Burns, Thomas, 1987-09-01, LFP-MN-R040
    - Levallee, Gerard; Burns, Thomas, 1987-09-01, LFP-MN-R041
    - Banford, Steve: St. Joseph's Cemetery, 1987-09-03, LFP-MN-R042
    - Banford, Steve: St. Joseph's Cemetery, 1987-09-03, LFP-MN-R043
    - Banford, Steve: St. Joseph's Cemetery, 1987-09-03, LFP-MN-R044
    - Banford, Steve: St. Joseph's Cemetery, 1987-09-03, LFP-MN-R045
    - Swinging Brass, 1987-08-06, LFP-MN-R046
    - Swinging Brass, 1987-08-06, LFP-MN-R047
    - Rurak, Tadeusz, 1987-09-08, LFP-MN-R048
    - Rurak, Tadeusz, 1987-09-08, LFP-MN-R049
    - Franco-American Male Chorus, 1987-09-08, LFP-MN-R050
    - Franco-American Male Chorus, 1987-09-08, LFP-MN-R051
    - Banks, Mendel, 1987-09-11, LFP-MN-R052
    - Banks, Mendel, 1987-09-11, LFP-MN-R053
    - Conway, Father Richard, 1987-08-21, LFP-TR-R001
    - Conway, Father Richard, 1987-08-21, LFP-TR-R002
    - Puerto Rican Festival, Music, 1987-08-21, LFP-TR-R003
    - Puerto Rican Festival, Music, 1987-08-21, LFP-TR-R004
    - Puerto Rican Festival, Music, 1987-08-21, LFP-TR-R005
    - Flag Raising, Puerto Rican Festival, 1987-08-22, LFP-TR-R006
    - Puerto Rican Festival, Music, 1987-08-22, LFP-TR-R007
    - Puerto Rican Festival, Music, 1987-08-22, LFP-TR-R008
    - Puerto Rican Festival, Music, 1987-08-22, LFP-TR-R009
    - Puerto Rican Festival, Music, 1987-08-22, LFP-TR-R010
    - Puerto Rican Festival, Music, 1987-08-22, LFP-TR-R011
    - Puerto Rican Festival, Music, 1987-08-22, LFP-TR-R012
    - Puerto Rican Festival, Music, 1987-08-22, LFP-TR-R013
    - New Hope Catholic Church, 1987-08-23, LFP-TR-R014
    - New Hope Catholic Church, 1987-08-23, LFP-TR-R015
    - New Hope Catholic Church, 1987-08-23, LFP-TR-R016
    - New Hope Catholic Church, 1987-08-23, LFP-TR-R017
    - Wallace, Gary and Tsitsianopoulos, Carol, 1987-08-25, LFP-TR-R018
    - Wallace, Gary and Tsitsianopoulos, Carol, 1987-08-25, LFP-TR-R019
    - Ramalho, Arthur, 1987-08-28, LFP-TR-R020
    - Ramalho, Arthur, 1987-08-28, LFP-TR-R021
    - Chigas, George, 1987-09-03, LFP-TR-R022
    - Chigas, George, 1987-09-03, LFP-TR-R023
    - Holy Ghost Society Park, 1987-08-05, LFP-TR-R024
    - Holy Ghost Society Park, 1987-08-05, LFP-TR-R025
    - Holy Ghost Society Park, 1987-08-05, LFP-TR-R026
    - Holy Ghost Society Park, 1987-08-05, LFP-TR-R027
    - Holy Ghost Society Park, 1987-08-05, LFP-TR-R028
    - Holy Ghost Society Park, 1987-08-05, LFP-TR-R029
    - Holy Ghost Society Park, 1987-08-05, LFP-TR-R030
    - St. Anthony's Church, 1987-09-06, LFP-TR-R031
    - St. Anthony's Church, 1987-09-06, LFP-TR-R032
    - Feast of Our Lady of Loreto Procession, 1987-08-06, LFP-TR-R033
    - Feast of Our Lady of Loreto Procession, 1987-08-06, LFP-TR-R034
    - Holy Ghost Park, Festival, 1987-09-06, LFP-TR-R035
    - Holy Ghost Park, Festival, 1987-09-06, LFP-TR-R036
    - Holy Ghost Park, Festival, 1987-09-06, LFP-TR-R037
    - Schmidt, Steve, 1987-09-09, LFP-TR-R038
    - Schmidt, Steve, 1987-09-09, LFP-TR-R039
    - Tymowicz, Joe and Lina, 1987-09-11, LFP-TR-R040
    - Tymowicz, Joe and Lina, 1987-09-11, LFP-TR-R041
    - Tymowicz, Joe and Lina, 1987-09-11, LFP-TR-R042
    - Tymowicz, Joe and Lina, 1987-09-11, LFP-TR-R043
    - Harley, Edward, 1987-09-17, LFP-DT-R001
    - Harley, Edward, 1987-09-17, LFP-DT-R002
    - Taffe, Richard, 1987-09-17, LFP-DT-R003
    - Taffe, Richard, 1987-09-17, LFP-DT-R004
    - Taffe, Richard, 1987-09-17, LFP-DT-R005
    - Taffe, Richard, 1987-09-17, LFP-DT-R006
    - Ignacio, Claire and Beausoleil, Joseph, 1987-09-22, LFP-DT-R007
    - Ignacio, Claire and Beausoleil, Joseph, 1987-09-22, LFP-DT-R008
    - Ignacio, Claire and Beausoleil, Joseph, 1987-09-22, LFP-DT-R009
    - Ignacio, Claire and Beausoleil, Joseph, 1987-09-22, LFP-DT-R010
    - Mercier, George, 1987-09-23, LFP-DT-R011
    - Mercier, George, 1987-09-23, LFP-DT-R012
    - Mercier, George, 1987-09-23, LFP-DT-R013
    - Giavis, Vassilios "Bill", 1988-03-23, LFP-DT-R014
    - Giavis, Vassilios "Bill", 1988-03-23, LFP-DT-R015
    - Giavis, Vassilios "Bill", 1988-03-23, LFP-DT-R016
    - Minorgan, Mary, 1988-03-29, LFP-DT-R017
    - Minorgan, Mary, 1988-03-29, LFP-DT-R018
    - Minorgan, Mary, 1988-03-29, LFP-DT-R019
    - Mercier, Armand, 1988-03-30, LFP-DT-R020
    - Mercier, Armand, 1988-03-30, LFP-DT-R021
    - Mercier, Armand, 1988-03-30, LFP-DT-R022
    - Mattheos, Dimitrios, 1988-04-01, LFP-DT-R023
    - Mattheos, Dimitrios, 1988-04-01, LFP-DT-R024
    - Mattheos, Dimitrios, 1988-04-01, LFP-DT-R025
    - Mattheos, Dimitrios, 1988-04-01, LFP-DT-R026
    - DeSousa, Henry, 1988-04-02, LFP-DT-R027
    - DeSousa, Henry, 1988-04-02, LFP-DT-R028
    - DeSousa, Henry, 1988-04-02, LFP-DT-R029
    - DeSousa, Henry, 1988-04-02, LFP-DT-R030
    - Hellenic-American School, 1988-04-04, LFP-DT-R031
    - Hellenic-American School, 1988-04-04, LFP-DT-R032
    - Hellenic-American School, 1988-04-04, LFP-DT-R033
- Series IV: Graphic Images
  - Black-and-White Photographs
    Photographed by Peter Bartis, Michael Bell, John Lueders-Booth, Douglas DeNatale, Barbara Fertig, Carl Fleischhauer, Mario Montaño, Martha Norkunas, Tom Rankin, David Taylor, Eleanor Wachs. See folders 106 to 119 for descriptions. Accession numbers: LFP-JB-B001 through LFP-TR-B487 Note: Accession numbers were assigned chronologically rather than by fieldworker.
    - Negatives, Approximately 1000 black-and-white negatives
      35mm negatives for all black-and-white images, identified by above accession numbers, are in two loose-leaf albums.
    - Contact sheets, 487 contact sheets in 24 folders
    - Black-and-White Prints, 100 8x10 black-and-white prints
      Fieldworkers at work; Lowell briefing; miscellaneous.
  - Color Slides and Photographs, Approximately 3,500 color slides and photographs
    Photographed by Michael Bell, John Lueders-Booth, Douglas DeNatale, Barbara Fertig, Carl Fleischhauer, Mario Montaño, Martha Norkunas, Tom Rankin, David Taylor, Eleanor Wachs. See folders 120 to 130 for folor-slide logs.
    Accession numbers:
    LFP-MB-C001 through LFP-MB-C004
    LFP-JB-C001 through LFP-JB-C081
    LFP-DD-C001 through LFP-DD-C040
    LFP-BF-C001
    LFP-CF-C001 through LFP-CF-C004
    LFP-MM-C001 through LFP-MM-C018
    LFP-MN-C001 through LFP-MN-C013
    LFP-TR-C001 through LFP-TR-C036 and
    LFP-TR-C053 through LFP-TR-C098
    LFP-DT-C001 through LFP-DT-C017
    LFP-EW-C001 through LFP-EW-C002.
    - Color slides, Approximately 3,490 35mm color slides housed in 262 folders
    - Color slide "phoney fiche", 41 "phoney fiche" (photographic index to all color slides)
    - Color prints, 16 color prints
    - Color negatives, 16 negatives
Item Numbering System
A numbering system for sound recordings and graphic images was used for the Lowell Folklife Project and they are arranged alphabetically by the last name of the fieldworker. The following codes are used:
LFP: Lowell Folklife Project
Fieldworker Initials:
MB: Michael Bell
JB: John Lueders-Booth
DD: Douglas DeNatale
BF: Barbara Fertig
CF: Carl Fleischhauer
MM: Mario Montaño
MN: Martha Norkunas
TR: Tom Rankin
RA: Refugee Arts Group
DT: David Taylor
EW: Eleanor Wachs
Document Type:
A: audiocassette
B: back and white negatives
C: color slide
CC: dubbed copy of loaned tape
R: reel-to-reel